gabrielash.com 2018-10-21

# Privacy Statement – Gabriel Ash

## Use of Information

Gabriel Ash ("The Company") will only use information collected about you in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) Privacy Policy and any other applicable legislation. 

We take the privacy of all staff, suppliers, customers and prospects very seriously. In order to carry out our day to day business legally, safely and efficiently, we need to obtain and store personal as well as corporate data. To allow us to send information and quotations to customers and interested parties we need to store contact details which typically include names, email addresses, telephone numbers and postal addresses.

On initial contact through our website or telephone customers and prospects will be asked to confirm their agreement to this data collection via opting in. This information will be used to contact the interested party with quotations, samples and other promotional literature that they have requested. Periodically we may contact you with further offers. By agreeing to our terms, you agree to the capture and retention of such information that may identify you as an individual, understanding that it will be used lawfully in the furtherance of a legitimate interest in and by Gabriel Ash Ltd. Contact details will never be shared by us with third parties. At any time, customers may request that we delete the data we hold on them, and this will be carried out promptly and in full. To remove your details data from our database please contact [enquiries@gabrielash.com](mailto:enquiries@gabrielash.com) or telephone 01829 271888.

## The Company's Products or Services

After you have opted in you may opt-out by sending the Company an e-mail at [enquiries@gabrielash.com](mailto:enquiries@gabrielash.com) calling us on 01829 271888, or writing to the company at the following address:

Gabriel Ash  
Monument Farm  
Farndon  
Chester  
CH3 6QP

The Company may also use and disclose information in aggregate (so that no individuals are identified) for marketing and strategic development purposes. We do not send random marketing emails to personal email addresses (spam).

## Use of Cookies

At present the Company does not use cookies although the Company reserves the right to use cookies to identify you when you visit this Website, track your browsing patterns and build up a demographic profile of your business. 

A cookie is a small piece of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive which enables the Company to know when you visit this website. Use of cookies also allows you as a registered user of this website to be presented with a personalised version of this website, carry out transactions and have access to information about your account. 

Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies. If you do this please look at the help menu on your browser. However, switching off cookies may restrict your use of this Website.

## Disclosure

The Company does not disclose information about you or your business to any third parties unless required to do so by government bodies and law enforcement agencies.  

## Links

This Website may contain links to other websites which are outside the Company's control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their own privacy policy.  

## Access Right

If you have opted in to our marketing via telephone/web contact or e-mail you have a right to access the personal data held about you. To obtain a copy of the personal information held about you by the Company, please write to

Gabriel Ash  
Monument Farm  
Farndon  
Chester  
CH3 6QP

Alternatively, you can e-mail [enquiries@gabrielash.com](mailto:enquiries@gabrielash.com)
